Andrew Sibiriakov

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Frontend developer with extensive experience in building SPAs using React, Redux and TypeScript since 2019. Strong problem-solving abilities and keen attention to detail. Excellent teammate. Active Codewars participant, demonstrating a genuine passion for his work.



1

+1 832-457-9872



andrey.sibiriakov@gmail.com



Houston, Texas



andrew-sib.com

SKILLS

- React / Redux / TypeScript
- HTML / CSS / Material UI / Tailwind
- REST API / Axios
- Next
- Docker
- Git
- Jest, Behave
- Atlassian / GitHub / GitLab
- Photoshop / Figma / GIMP

EDUCATION

MOSCOW TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY, MTUCI

Bachelor's degree - Information Systems and Technologies (2018 - 2022)

IT-INCUBATOR, MINSK, BELARUS

React front end development course (2020 - 2021)

LANGUAGES

English, Russian

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

ChipAssist

2021 - Present

- Built a marketplace of electronic parts (chipassist.com)
- Built a stock exchange for sellers of electronic parts (requests.chipassist.com)
- Built an admin panel for our associates
- Built a complex system for chatting between buyers and sellers
- Testing
- Deployment to production
- Support and mentoring of junior specialists

HTML DEVELOPER / CONTENT MANAGER

Freelance

2019 - 2021

- Creation of landing pages and parts of websites (product cards, forms, navigation menus, etc.)
- Creation of graphic content
- Design development